Hill, James C. Additional Files 5703
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
James C. Hill Additional Files
1973-1978
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Hill, James C.
5703
15 cubic feet
15 linear ft.
Records (documents).
3122663
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 19, 2003
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 28, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5538: James C. Hill Arbitration Files
Arbitration, Industrial -- United States -- Sources; Hill, James C., 1914-
3122663
- Alleghany Port Authority - Budd Co (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Chaplin and Bangs Co. - Lettick (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Midtown Chev. - NYC Board of Ed., 1973 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- NYC Board, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- NYC Board, 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- NYC Board, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- NYC Board, 1976-1978 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- NYC Committee - Owens III. (Box 8, Folder 1)
- PPG Industry - Puerto Rico (Box 9, Folder 1)
- RCA Corp. - West Virginia (Box 10, Folder 1)
- American Arbitration Ass'n. (Box 11, Folder 1)
- American Arbitration Ass'n. (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Arbitrability (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Arbitration Award Forms (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Arbitration Cases, Awards (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Arbitration, General (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Arbitration, General (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Arbitration - Hershey Foods (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Arbitration - Notes-Issues, Sub. (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Arbitration - Notes on Issues (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Arbitration - Pitfalls to Avoid (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Atomic Energy - Labor (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Automation (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Background Materials (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Bibliography (Box 11, Folder 15)
- B.N.A. - Labor Arbitration Reports (Box 11, Folder 16)
- CB Agreements - General (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Civil Rights and Labor (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Collective Bargaining (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Compulsory Arbitration (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Construction (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Discipline - Discharge (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Discipline - Discharge (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Emergency Boards (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Emergency Boards - Railway (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Fact Finding (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Featherbedding (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Fringe Benefits (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Grievance Procedures (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Hiring Practices (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Insurance (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Jurisdictional Disputes (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Labor Law - Current File (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Labor Law (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Malapropos (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Mediate ion (Box 13, Folder 2)
- New York City (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Public Employment - Bargaining Unit (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Public Employment - Canada (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Public Employment - N.J. - Perc. (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Public Employment - Saratoga Conf. (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Public Employment - Taylor Law (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Spidr (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Taft - Hartley (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Wage Reopening Arbitration (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Wallen, Saul Memorial (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Work Rules (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Arbitration Conferences (Box 14, Folder 1)
- BiIIing Information (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Community Disputes - NY (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Cornell Univ. - Coll. Bargaining. (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Readings Cornell Univ. - IBEW (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Correspondence - General (Box 14, Folder 6)
- ERISA (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Form Letters (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Ind. ReIations. Society (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Miscellaneous (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Miscellaneous (Box 14, Folder 11)
- National Academy of Arbitration (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Photos (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Public Employee Relations Bd. (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Speeches (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Speeches (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Altieri, James (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Altieri, James (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Bailer, Lloyd (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Ben Scheiber, Israel (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Christensen, Thomas (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Feinberg, Robert (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Feinberg, Robert (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Feinberg, Robert (Box 14, Folder 24)
- Friedman. Milton (Box 14, Folder 25)
- Friedman, MiIton (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Friedman, MiIton (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Horvitz, Aaron (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Rock, Eli (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Rock, Eli (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Rubin, MiIton (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Rubin, MiIton (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Ruffe, PhiIip (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Seitz, Peter (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Sovern, Michael (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Stark, Arthur (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Stockmen, Abram (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Stockmen, Abram (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Trotta, Maurice (Box 15, Folder 14)
- WoIf, Benjamin (Box 15, Folder 15)
- WoIf, Benjamin (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Miscellaneous (other arbitrators) (Box 15, Folder 17)